## ALEKSANDR KORSHUNOV

Phone: +972-50-48-50-222
Email: aleks.corshunov@gmail.com
Website: corshunov.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/corshunov
GitHub: github.com/corshunov

### SUMMARY

Enthusiastic and meticulous software engineer with 3+ years of experience. Being the only programmer in the division, developed and maintain 10+ projects with 10K+ lines of code as well as reduced manual steps to 0 of various business processes.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

>>> Israel

Software Engineer at Ayalon Highways Co. Aug 2017 - present

- models

- ci/cd
- agile flow
- knowledge system
- models laboratory website and repos

>>> Russia

Mar 2016 - Jul 2017 Highway Design Engineer Transportation Engineer Sep 2013 - Mar 2016

EDUCATION

- Data Science and Machine Learning 2019 - 2020 Yandex School of Data Science YDATA (Israel)

- M.Sc. in Information Systems and Technologies 2015 - 2017 Siberian Transport University (Russia), GPA 5.0

- B.Sc. in Civil Engineering 2011 - 2015 Siberian Transport University (Russia), GPA 4.95

#### SKILLS

- Languages: C, C++, C#, Python, Javascript, SQL
- DevOps: Linux, Windows, Bash, Docker, Kubernetes, CI/CD, Azure, AWS
- Web: HTML5, CSS3, Node.js, Django, Postgres, MongoDB
- Tools: Scrum, Git, Vim, Tmux, i3 Data Science: Numpy, Pandas, Scikit-learn, Spacy, PySpark, Tensorflow, PyTorch, NLTK
- Transport software: INRO EMME and Dynameq, Caliper TransCAD, Aimsun Next, Eclipse SUMO, AutoCAD

## EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- madrich at Jewish children camp (2017)
- volunteer at Olympic Games (2014), Formula 1 (2015), Universiade (2013, 2017), and other events
- captain of youth professional football team (2006 2008)

# LANGUAGES

Hebrew: basic English: advanced Russian: native